So away from power!
Off you go!
And this is so interesting.
That in this power, one often talks about the angry young men
They often talk about these violent rebellion.
But in fact, we see that women's ability to organize themselves - and for that matter men who
Organizes - in the diligent organizational work.
There is a key that we often overlook.
[Is popular rebellion part of democracy?]
Popular rebellion is part of democratization processes.
Or it can be, we should say.
Therefore, it also becomes a way;
That when people see that it is not possible to influence in other ways.
So it is very positive that people mobilize themselves.